Hello everyone Good evening How to wish
Всем привет Добрый вечер Как пожелать
normally I'm from the city of Khmelnitsky
нормально Я из города Хмельницкий
Ukraine Where are you from I'm from the city of Moscow
Украина Вы откуда Я из города Москвы
Russia naturally but some people say
Россия естественно но некоторые говорят
there's the Moscow Republic or Zalesie
там Московская республика или Залесье
a lot of people you're talking to all sorts of
много вы с кем разговариваете всех
hospitals with people from Russia
больницы с людьми из России там всякие
Well maybe there's all sorts I don't know
есть Ну может быть есть всякие не знаю
any  I do
никакой Московской Республики мне
n’t know any Moscow Republic from the forest. Well, what kind of
неизвестно из леса никакого Ну а какая у
republic do you have? I have the Russian
вас республика у меня Российская
Federation, there are
Федерация
republics, the Republic of Bashkortostan,
есть республики республика Башкортостан
there are cities of federal significance, the Russian
есть города федерального значения
Republic is what, there is no
русская республика это какая нет никакой
Russian
русской Республики
Republic. The Russians don’t have their own republic, the Russians
Русских нет своей республики у русских
have Russia. The
есть Россия
Constitution says this is a country of
вас Конституции написано это страна
multinational people, the Russian
многонационального народа Российской
Federation.
Федерации
and that yes, it doesn’t say that this is a country of
и что да там не написано что это страна
Russians, but there is, yes,
русских но есть да
you figure out what the question is first, I’ll
ты разбери сначала в чем вопрос я тебя
untangle you, I’ll help you. Look, for
распутываю помогу тебе Смотри вот
example, the
например
Russian Federation is the country of all
Российская Федерация это страна всех
Russia Russian
Россия русских
gypsies,
цыгантов
separately the Tatars have national ones, I have a
отдельно есть национальные у татарства я
Republic of Chechens The Russians don’t have their own
Республику чеченцев Русских нет своей
republic
республики
and the gypsies  we don’t have our own republic Yes, we do
и у цыган нет своей республики Да мы не
n’t strive to have our own republic, we don’t have we looked at the republic for the
у нас нет у нас смотрели республика для
Russian people, it’s too small, the
русских людей это слишком мало русские
Russians are a civilization. You see, even the state is not enough for the Russians, even the Russians are a
государство мало русским даже русские -
separate civilization, so Russia
это отдельная цивилизация поэтому Россия
Look, Chechen, Ukrainian, Georgian, Buryat,
Вот смотри чеченец украинец грузин бурят
this is the noun word who  current
это существительное слово кто течение
who Buryat who is American and Russian is
кто бурят кто американец а русский это
an adjective which which
прилагательное какой какой
Rehabilitation that is
Реабилитационный то есть
Russian Armenian Russians Ukraine is
русский армянин русские Украине есть
Russian no Russians are Russians but there
русский нет русские русские но
were Russians Chechen Russians were and Russian
русские чеченец русские были а русские
Russians are not oil butter it
русские нет масло масло
turns out Russian novel Ramzan Kadyrov Russian
получается русский роман Рамзан Кадыров
he is Russian Chechen he is Russian
русский он русский чеченец он русский
honor he is Chechen by nationality  but
честь он по национальности чеченец но
belonging to the Russian civilization
принадлежность к русской цивилизации
I am hearing for the first time that Ramzan Kadyrov
я Впервые слышу что Рамзан Кадыров
that he is Russian he belongs to the Russian
что он русский он принадлежит к русской
civilization again you right now,
цивилизации еще раз ты вот сейчас ну
think about it, this is a very mop can hear
подумай это очень швабра может услышать
Ramzan Kadyrov is Russian Chechen he is
Рамзан Кадыров это русский чеченецкое он
Russian gets Russian Buryats
русский получает русские бурят
Kadyrov killed 16 years before the first Russian
Кадыров до первого русского убил 16 лет
He killed  Russian Russian or Russian
Он убил русского русского или русского
Chechen
чеченца
you confuse the difference
путаешь разницу
Ramzan Kadyrov said that he killed
Рамзан Кадыров говорил что он убил
the first Russian 16 years old he was the Russian
первого русского 16 лет это он русского
Russian killed the Russian Buryat
русского убил русского бурята
could have killed the Russian Buryat could have killed the
мог убить русского бурята мог убить
Russian Ukrainian could have killed the Russian Russian
русского украинца мог убить русского
Russian is not just Russian Well,
русского не бывает просто русский Ну а
which one is he talking about? So I was the first
про какого говорит Вот я был первый
Russian,
русского
I also study civilizations, but
я я тоже изучаю цивилизации по то вот
look,
смотри
I can’t. When there is a conversation about
я не смогу Я когда разговор про
civilizations, my inner
цивилизации идёт у меня внутренний
scientist wakes up and I start, uh, as if
учёный просыпается и я начинаю э как бы
scientists are not really there,
учёные на самом деле нет
I’m Russian, I’m not a Russian scientist Yes,
я я русский не русский учёный Да потому
because I understand what the
что вот понял в чём
ideological concept is  such a scientific
идеологическая концепция такая научная
if, for example, there is
если например есть
Ramzan Kadyrov, he is Russian, Chechen, yes, and
Рамзан Кадырова он русские чеченец да А
for example, this Lavrov, he is a Russian Armenian, yes, and for example,
например этот Лавров он русский армянин
Vladimir Putin, he is
да А например Владимир Путин он русский
Russian, yes, for example, he is Russian. Is
вептся да например вот он русский
there an operational affiliation or
А есть операционная принадлежность или
not? Look, what is
нет Да смотри Какая национальная у
Putin’s nationality? He is Russian and his civilizational
Путина Он русский а цивилизационная
affiliation is Russian.  then he is Russian
принадлежность он русский то он русский
Russian
русский
YouTube, driving us through Kar Georgiev into a
YouTube загоняя нас через кар Георгиев в
shadow ban and a very rich appearance is not
теневый бан и дужебогатого вида не
shown to people in private,
показывается людям в частном на
information about streams is shown
показывается информация про стримы тому
in order for the little operational little animal
для того чтобы мало оперативный зверезок
Sign right at a time and there is an attempt there in a
Подпишите прям за раз а попыт там в
kilogram about Cream video
килограмме о Крим видео
information and we would take it out  you are attracted
информация и мы бы вынес вам аттраматы
by stylish
по стильной
operational stars are not included, we
оперативный звездок не заложено это
will show you the YouTube word to Ukraine
покажем вам YouTube слово Украине